we have been getting in a lot of data
from the insurance pack as well of
course uh the non-life insurance data
was out and some of the life insurance
companies have also managed to report
their numbers let's go across to anurag
to get the details of the latest numbers
which are coming out hi
anurag non-life Insurance sector has
shown a robust growth in month of
September the premium has go grown by
25% from last year 21,000 CR this year
September premium is 26,400 CR and if we
talk about the first six month of this
fiscal the premium growth is
18% uh the premium has reached up to 1
lakh 37,000 CR from last year's 1 lakh
16,000 CR if we talk about the listed
space Also then uh New India Assurance
has shown a 8% growth in first six month
and in month of September the premium
growth is 11% icsi Lombard has shown 18%
growth in first six month and in month
of September the premium growth is 13%
apart from this star Health has also
shown uh premium growth of 18% uh so uh
this is uh the private insurance
companies have shown a a tremendous
growth in the month of September which
has converted into a very good set of
numb for listed companies also if you
talk about the life insurance space also
they have also uh reported a good number
I Pro and LC uh numbers are weak but a
good set of numbers has shown by Max
life insurance and SBI life
insurance thanks for highlighting all
those details H mop saying that the
recent news item regarding to the F fire
against the company is an old matter
which pertains to all the way back to
2009 uh and 10